Did you know
that the very first
Google Doodle
wasn't a planned
celebration, but
a mischievous cry
for help? Back in
1998, founders
Larry Page and
Sergey Brin were
heading out to
Burning Man, the
wild and wacky
festival in the
Black Rock Desert.
They wanted to
let users know
they were out
of office, but
with a typical
Google twist. So,
they plopped a
stick figure
drawing of a
burning man
behind the Google
logo. It was
meant to be a
quick and silly
thing, but it
ended up sparking
a tradition that
now sees Doodles
grace the homepage
for everything from
major holidays
to obscure historical
figures. Who knew
a little Burning
Man burner could
ignite such a
creative firestorm?
So next time you
see a Doodle,
remember its humble
beginnings: a playful
wink from the
Google founders,
reminding us that
even the biggest tech giants
can have a bit of fun.